{
    "subject": "Norman_Mailer",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Maidstone__film_",
    "human_readable": "Norman Mailer created the film Maidstone.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9005265831947327,
            "question": "Who created the film Maidstone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8157546520233154,
            "question": "What is the connection between Norman Mailer and the film Maidstone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7965742349624634,
            "question": "What is the name of the film created by Norman Mailer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6215016841888428,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Norman Mailer."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5715110898017883,
            "question": "Is Norman Mailer known for writing or filmmaking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5709564685821533,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Norman Mailer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47215065360069275,
            "question": "What type of work did Norman Mailer produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43207401037216187,
            "question": "What was Norman Mailer's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43147414922714233,
            "question": "Did Norman Mailer work in literature or cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33823081851005554,
            "question": "Besides writing, what other creative pursuit did Norman Mailer engage in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Norman Mailer created the film Maidstone.",
            "html": "yago_28873_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Norman Mailer work in literature or cinema?",
            "html": "yago_28873_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Norman Mailer's profession?",
            "html": "yago_28873_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of work did Norman Mailer produce?",
            "html": "yago_28873_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28873_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28873_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28873_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28873_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28873_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28873_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28873_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28873_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28873_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28873_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis indicates that the triple is supported by the documents, and therefore the response is affirmative. The documents indeed mention Norman Mailer as the creator of the film Maidstone."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information across multiple documents supports that Norman Mailer was involved in creating the film \"Maidstone,\" both as a writer and director, and even starred in it. Therefore, the triple stating that Norman Mailer created the film Maidstone is correct according to the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}